Guide to the Danbury Industrial Corporation Records MS 050
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series VI: Correspondence
  - General Correspondence
    - Publicity Correspondence & Misc., 1964; MS 050.1_5_11_x (Box 9, Folder 12)
      1964 Mass mailings D.I.C.
    - R.Gretsch Correspondence, 1964-1965; MS 050.1_5_12_x (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - D.I.C. Correspondence, estate related., 1939-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Recording of Wills, Transfer of stock
    - D.I.C. Correspondence (A - C) - issuance of stock, 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Accessioned with Real Estate materials.
    - Real Estate opportunities, 1941-1946 (Box 10, Folder 3 - 6)
      Real Estate Pamphlets; Real Estate Appraisers Cost Data; Letters; Postcards; Wills; Property Notes
  - D.I.C. Stock correspondence
    - Lost Stock Certificates, 1950-1955 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Contains copies of wills, stock certificates, and financial statements for stock holders. Correspondence includes materials from Harold Meeker, Arthur Hodgson, etc.
    - Stock Transfer Inquiries, 1928-1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      2015 Accession.
    - Stock Transfer Inquiries, 1928-1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Stock Transfer Inquiries, 1954-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Stock Transfer Inquiries, 1949-1955 (Box 14, Folder 5-8)
    - Stock Transfer Inquiries, 1953-1969 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence regarding the purchase of stock, 1963-1966 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Canceled certificates, 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lists of Shares and Shareholders (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Dividends Correspondence, 139-1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Series VII: Oversized
  - Blueprints, Maps and Drawings, 1920s-1960s; MS 050.1_OS 1_1_x (Folder OS 1, Item 1-19)
    Items removed from other folders where noted - mostly from corporate client files.
    D.I.C. Municipal taxes 1949-1951
    Stoney Hill Corp. drawn map of Eagle Road
    Commerce Park, Danbury Industrial Park, Seymour Power Blueprint
    Study Print relocation of Rt 25 Monroe/New Town, 1969
    Map of New Town, 1956
    Connecticut Research Center Map
    Neumann Endler blueprint - second story addition
    Addition to Danbury Rubber Co. (2), 1946
    Proposed addition to factory (Danbury Rubber Corp.?), 1944
    Site Plan for Danbury Square Box, 1969
    Blueprints for offices and plant (?), 1969
    Drawn maps of Backus Ave. and railroad
    Blueprints for D.I.C. roof plans, 1950 (3)
    Shelter Rock Road Map, 1950
    Buiding zoning map - Bethel, CT
    Park Avenue Map
    Blueprint New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad (right of way track map at Bethel, CT), 1915 (2)
    Blueprint New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad- South End of Danbury, 1945-1946
    Blueprint Neuman-Endler Inc. (from Real Estate folders accessioned 2015)
- Series VIII: Miscellaneous
  - Trimpert, Raymond. "A Study of Danbury's Industrial Transition"; Western Connecticut State College Thesis: Danbury, CT. 1969., MS 050.1_1_6_x (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Connecticut Development News, 1972; MS 050.1_1_7_x (Box 1, Item 7)
    6 pg. pamphlet
  - Town of Danbury: Plan of Development - Technical Planning Associates, 1960; MS 050.1_1_8_x (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Town of Danbury: Plan of Development - Technical Planning Associates, 1967; MS 050.1_1_9_x (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Abstract of Title - Bridget Regan Shelter Rock Road, 1930s; MS 050.1_1_10_x (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Danbury Title Company title search
  - Abstract of Title - Michael Hurd 36 Shelter Rock Road, 1930s; MS 050.1_1_11_x (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Original storage boxes for financial records and some correspondence., undated (Binder 1-6)
    6 boxes with faux bound volume spine